// select elements

// add questions
let questions = [
    {
      question: "Where does Michael Scott move to start his new life with Holly?",
      choiceA: "New York, New York",
      choiceB: "Los Angeles, California",
      choiceC: "Boulder, Colorado",
      choiceD: "Salt Lake City, Utah",
      correct: "C"
      },
    {
      question: "Which of these is NOT a name of one Angela's cats?",
      choiceA: "Bandit",
      choiceB: "Sprinkles",
      choiceC: "Petals",
      choiceD: "Oreo",
      correct: "D"
    },
    {
      question: "At Phyllis' wedding, Michael revealed that her nickname in high school was what?",
      choiceA: "Perfectly Adequate",
      choiceB: "Easy Rider",
      choiceC: "OCD Girl",
      choiceD: "Belle",
      correct: "B"
    },
    {
      question: "Michael and Dwight tried to steal clients from which local competing business?",
      choiceA: "Staples",
      choiceB: "Pendelton",
      choiceC: "Catalyst Paper",
      choiceD: "Prince Family Paper",
      correct: "D"
    },
    {
      question: "Finish Dwight's security code: “The tea in Nepal is very hot, but the coffee in ______ is much hotter.",
      choiceA: "Cuba",
      choiceB: "Cebu",
      choiceC: "Peru",
      choiceD: "Brazil",
      correct: "C"
    },
    {
      question: "Which Harry Potter book did Dwight say he'd take to a desert island?",
      choiceA: "Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban",
      choiceB: "Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix",
      choiceC: "Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince",
      choiceD: "Harry Potter and the Sorcerer's Stone",
      correct: "A"
    },
    {
      question: "While playing who would you do in the office, Michael says he’d have sex with which coworker?",
      choiceA: "Pam",
      choiceB: "Angela",
      choiceC: "Ryan",
      choiceD: "Danny",
      correct: "C"
    },
    {
      question: "Who won the last 'Hottest in the Office Dundie Award'?",
      choiceA: "Ryan Howard",
      choiceB: "Pam Beesly",
      choiceC: "Danny Cordray",
      choiceD: "Michael Scott",
      correct: "C"
    },
    {
      question: "What does Dwight say is the scariest animal?",
      choiceA: "Black Bear",
      choiceB: "Lions",
      choiceC: "Sharks",
      choiceD: "Box Jellyfish",
      correct: "D"
    },
    {
      question: "Why is Michael afraid to move to Colorado?",
      choiceA: "He's going to miss his Dunder Mifflin family.",
      choiceB: "The TV channels will be in the wrong order.",
      choiceC: "He'll never see Ryan again.",
      choiceD: "He doesn't know anyone is Colorado",
      correct: "B"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the title of the movie Michael Scott makes?",
      choiceA: "Level One: Midnight",
      choiceB: "Michael Scorn",
      choiceC: "Nightmare in  Scranton",
      choiceD: "Threat Level Midnight",
      correct: "D"
    },
    {
      question: "When Dwight is explaining his perfect crime, what is the name of the girl?",
      choiceA: "Tawny",
      choiceB: "Taylor",
      choiceC: "Tiffany",
      choiceD: "Tammy",
      correct: "C"
    },
    {
      question: "In the “Diversity Day” episode, what famous comedian’s stand up routine does Michael imitate?",
      choiceA: "Chris Rock",
      choiceB: "Dave Chappelle",
      choiceC: "Louis C.K.",
      choiceD: "Ricky Gervis",
      correct: "A"
    },
    
]

// variables

// start quiz functions

// render progress

// counter render

// check answers

// if the answer is correct

// if the answer is wrong

// score

// percentage of correct answers

// images for the final score tally

// invoke the code